

KATHRYN FERRUGIA

Ever evolving web developer. Passionate about improving user experience. Equal ability to perform autonomously, as a supportive team player or a team leader. Successfully lobbied to extend the Indiana Girls High School lacrosse season. Awarded Metro Atlantic Athletic Conference 1999 Women's Lacrosse Coach of the Year.

Agile Scrum Bootstrap C# HTML JavaScript

ASP.NET MVC Brackets CSS InVision Sketch App

Adobe: InDesign Illustrator Photoshop LightRoom XD

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft .NET SmarStart

Eleven Fifty Academy, Fishers, IN October 2017 - January 2018

Todah Blog: Worked with small team of developers to create blog webside for client (Python, Django, CSS & Bootstrap) Event Scheduler: Designed web application for scheduling events (C#, ASP.NET, CSS, Razor)

Various application development excercises utilizing HTML, CSS, HTML, JavaScript

UX Design

Career Foundry, online August 2016 - August 2016

Worked closely with mentor to I develop a mock, mobile first, time management app. content writing, color board, mood board, user profiles, workflow, wireframes,

Paralegal Certificate

Duke University, online August 2013 - August 2014

M.P.A., Criminal Justice

Indiana University/Purdue University, Indianapolis,IN

August 2000 - May 2010

B.A., American History

Hobart and William Smith Colleges, Geneva, NY September 1988 - June 1992

WORK EXPERIENCE

Curriculum Developer, Intern

Eleven Fifty Academy, Indianapolis , IN February 2018 - present

Created curriculum documentation for advanced CSS concepts using Markdown and Gitbook Designed code examples for curriculum demonstrating concepts

Paralegal

Hall, Render, Killian, Heath & Lyman, P.C., Indianapolis, IN January 2016 - June 2016

Managed database for attorneys serving health care supply chain companies. Tracked attorney case assignments

Lacrosse Coach

North Central High School, Indianapolis, IN

2001 - 2012
Fairfield University, Fairfield, CT

1996 - 1998

Scheduled games, reviewed GPAs to determine eligibility, and coordinated medical release forms Managed equipment inventory and purchasing, developed lesson plans and orchestrated game site set-up Manage games and executed all-day, multi-team events.

Email: Phone: kcvferrugia@gmail.com 317.508.5228

LinkedIn: Website:

kcv-ferrugia-b46a903a kcvferrugia.github.io/Portfolio

VOLUNTEER LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Event Chair, Committee Member, Lobsterpalooza, Indianapolis Opera Board Member, U12 Coordinator, Glendale Soccer Association Substitute teacher, St. Pius X School, Indianapolis, IN Vice President, Indiana Girls Lacrosse Association President, New England College Women's Lacrosse Association